Social media can be a powerful communication tool for employees, helping them to collaborate, share ideas and solve problems.
对员工来说，社交媒体可以成为一种强大的沟通工具，帮助他们协作、分享想法和解决问题。
Research has shown that 82% of employees think social media can improve work relationships and 60% believe it can support decision-making processes.
研究表明，82%的员工认为社交媒体能够改善工作关系，60%的员工相信它能够为决策过程提供支持。
These beliefs contribute to a majority of workers connecting with colleagues on social media, even during work hours.
这些看法促使大多数员工在社交媒体上与同事联系，甚至在工作时间也是如此。
Employers typically worry that social media is a productivity killer; more than half of U.S. employers reportedly block access to social media at work.
雇主通常担心社交媒体是工作效率的杀手；据报道，美国一半以上的雇主在工作场所禁止访问社交媒体。
In my research with 277 employees of a healthcare organization I found these concerns to be misguided.
我以一家医疗保健机构的277名员工为对象开展研究，发现这些担忧是错误的。
Social media doesn’t reduce productivity nearly as much as it kills employee retention.
社交媒体对工作效率的损害，远不及它对员工留任的破坏那么严重。
In the first part of the study I surveyed the employees about why and how they used platforms like Facebook, Twitter, or LinkedIn.
在研究的第一部分，我调查了员工使用Facebook、Twitter、LinkedIn这类平台的原因和方式。
Respondents were then asked about their work behaviors, including whether they felt motivated in their jobs and showed initiative at work.
随后，受访者被问及自己的工作行为，包括是否对工作有干劲，以及是否在工作中表现出主动性。
I found employees who engage in online social interactions with co-workers through social media blogs tend to be more motivated and come up with innovative ideas.
我发现，通过社交媒体博客与同事开展线上社交互动的员工，往往更有干劲，并会提出创新的想法。
But when employees interact with individuals outside the organization, they are less motivated and show less initiative.
但员工如果与机构以外的人互动，干劲就没那么足，表现出的主动性也更少。
In the second part of the study I found 76% of employees using social media for work took an interest in other organizations they found on social media.
在研究的第二部分，我发现，为工作而使用社交媒体的员工中，有76%对自己在社交媒体上看到的其他机构产生了兴趣。
When I examined how respondents expressed openness to new careers and employers, I found that they engaged in some key activities including researching new organizations and making new work connections.
我考察了受访者如何表现出对新职业和新雇主的开放态度，发现他们会从事一些关键活动，包括调研新的机构、建立新的工作人脉。
These findings present a dilemma for managers: employees using social media at work are more engaged and more productive, but they are also more likely to leave your company.
这些发现给管理者出了一道难题：在工作中使用社交媒体的员工投入度更高、效率也更高，但也更有可能离开你的公司。
Managers should implement solutions that neutralize the retention risk caused by social media.
管理者应当实施一些解决方案，抵消社交媒体在留住员工方面带来的风险。
They can create social media groups in which employees will be more likely to collaborate and less likely to share withdrawal intentions or discussions about external job opportunities.
他们可以建立社交媒体群组，在这些群组里，员工协作的可能性会更大，而透露离职意向或谈论外部工作机会的可能性则会更小。
Managers can also use social media to directly reduce turnover intentions, by recognizing employees’ accomplishments and giving visibility to employees’ success stories.
管理者还可以利用社交媒体，通过表彰员工的成就、展示员工的成功事迹，直接降低员工的跳槽意向。